homechoice.co.za 2013-04-11

# Privacy Policy | HomeChoice

privacy policy 

We recognise that your privacy is very important to you. And we can assure you that it’s very important to us too. Below is our Privacy Policy. Make sure you read it carefully.

**How secure are my details?** ****  
HomeChoice guarantees that your privacy is protected throughout your journey around our website. We’ve gone to great lengths to ensure your card information is secure – and stays that way. Any card information you enter on our site is encrypted and protected with the best encryption software in the industry – Secure Sockets Layer (SSL). Encryption scrambles the information transmitted across the Internet, including your credit card number, name and address. We do not store any of your payment details on our site or server, but rather in an encrypted format on the MyGate server – a registered, secure Payment Service Provider (PSP).   
Remember: When entering any personal information, make sure you shop on a secure computer only and not at an internet café. 

When you enter the secure areas of the HomeChoice website, you will see a locked padlock symbol on your browser, usually at the bottom right-hand corner of your screen. This indicates that the screen is in secure mode and any details you provide on this screen will be encrypted for your security. 

**What do I need when I order?** ****  
This will depend on your choice of payment method – cash, credit card payment or purchasing on terms. Click here to see a table of the information we will need. 

**How do we use your personal information?** ****  
Your personal details are used to verify who you are, and to enable us to deliver any orders you place with us. It also helps understand your needs so that we may better service them. In addition to the ordering process we may ask users for personal information at other times including, without limitation, when you enter any promotional competitions or when you make a purchase using the HomeChoice website. Furthermore, if you contact us for any reason, we may keep a record of that communication. Should you participate in any online surveys, we may keep a record of the information provided by you. Your personal information may also be used by us for statistical analyses and marketing. HomeChoice may disclose personal information in response to a specific request by a law enforcement agency, subpoena, court order, or as required by law.

**Is my personal information kept confidential?** ****  
Yes, your information is kept strictly confidential and is never disclosed to third parties. Moreover, we will only contact you with news of HomeChoice special offers and promotions if you’ve indicated you would like to receive it. You are entitled, at any stage, to opt out of this service.

The HomeChoice website is backed by Thawte.

By using our site, you agree to the terms above.

**Questions** ****  
If you have any questions concerning our Privacy Policy, please don’t hesitate to contact us on   
0861 HOMECHOICE (0861 466324)

HomeChoice (Pty) Ltd 78 Main Rd, Wynberg, Cape Town, 7800
